Hello friends, hello everyone.  How are you
?  Hope everyone is doing well.
Friends, today we are going to buy goods.
Oh my wasp.
Look friends, I see it.
[MUSIC]
How did it get locked in the car?  I have an
old enmity with the truths.  Which is a round
mark here when I was little.
Then it was not cut properly.
Get out brother, get out.  At least his life was
saved for now.  Our people are going to Ghaziabad to
collect goods.  Friends, now
we will load the chain in the vehicle and
our Bharata Shri will help us in this.  The sun is shining very brightly today,
brother.  How is the younger one?   Take
out these big ones.  This one,
this one, it is clean and strong too.
I am coming and do one more thing,
put money in its tag, I will
save toll from here but I will go once,
how much time before,
okay I am doing it,
I will save toll from here but I will go
from peripheral to Dadri, there will be jam at Lal Kuan, there are
two CNG points, it will be done there
and I will tell you as soon as I reach here,
right now friends we are calling from
Ghaziabad and Ind Bhai how are you,
where did you bring this from, have
n't you called me and Ramu Bhaiya how are you,
move the car, it
is empty, note, there is a
delay of one hour and 15 minutes, right, no, it is
one hour and 15 minutes, you do it quickly,
I have to go, one more tension has come up,
I have to deal with that,
how much
Bhaiya, this is wrong.  You are busy getting your work done.
How much time will it take?
And
this is our bent one.   I don't
want this.   I don't
want this.  I am not going to take even a single white ball.   Please
take the white one down.   I don't
want this either.  You just empty it and fill it
quickly.
You empty it first.  Where is Ramu Bhaiya?
Friend, I have come from such a far distance and you are
not able to get your work done here.
Ramu Bhaiya,
O Ramu Bhai, I do
n't know where you have disappeared.
Right now friends, we are busy doing Bilsuri around Bilsuri.
Tell me
Lalpur
Lalpur CNG pump.
Put the nozzle on two and a half.   I am getting
CNG filled now.  Our Babu
is hungry.  Brother, put the nozzle on.
And they show each boy.  Show this.
What is there to show in these?  What's special?   The
best.
Look at it.  Like the meter will start from zero.   It will
start from zero.  Is there any way?
Not
from zero.   The
CNG meter will start from zero only.   If there is
some problem in between then it is a different matter.
Friends, I left Bulandshahr and
reached Secunderabad.  Could not make a video there.
Nor could I
complete any other work there.  Now what is the reason behind that
?  The reason is very brilliant and well-founded.  I will
show you now.  Friends, this is
Hyundai's Aura car number UP 13 CJ
9382.  This is our car.  Amit Kumar
is registered in my name.  This vehicle has met with an
accident on the peripheral.
19th, fifth month, if I am correct then it must have been
around 7:00 in the morning, the
axle of the car's left side front
broke, after which the brakes were suddenly applied and the car
overturned.  After turning over, the vehicle has hit three Kala Mandi
and after turning over, you must be seeing this roof, the
vehicle has dragged on the road for at least 150 meters.  After that the car stopped
because of a truck driver who was
driving his truck next to the car.  Friends, what do you have to do now
?  One special thing has to be taken care of.
This is gone.   Do
not buy ICICI Lombard insurance.
My request to all those who can hear me, see me, and know me, at any time in life, is to
never buy ICICI LBD insurance.  Do
not buy it at all.  Now, when they have
cancelled the claim, they have cancelled it by saying
that the vehicle is running well.  How high is running
?  Deepak, how old is our car?   It must be
1 and a half years old.   The
car is about 1 and a half years old.
What is the condition of the car from inside?
What is the condition inside?
Water is filling the entire car.
Yes, I was standing in the open in the rain.
Standing in the open, then what is their responsibility
in this?
Deepak Bhai.
Moving from inside.
Show video.
Hey, I made you forget and gave you something.  What are you saying?
Flow was ruined.
Yes.  This car is approximately one and a half years old.  It may vary a
little bit over the course of a few
months.  Now he cancelled the claim by saying this.  The
claim was cancelled as the
vehicle was running well.  If you look at the car exactly, it has
run between Rs 30 to 35,000.
Which is only for walking.  And
our work is such that our vehicle keeps running here and there.
Now suppose that the
tyre of the car bursts in Haridwar.  At 12:00
, 2:00, 3:00, 1:00 at night, no
one would come into anyone's sight.  Only our people will
go.  We have to take care of our own problems.   For
now, it will remain here.
Its case is in the court.  The date has been received.
As soon as any
updates come, I will keep updating you guys.   It is
filled with water and is
standing outside the showroom.  Will anyone stand there covered?  There was no separate vehicle of
ours
parked there, many vehicles were parked there and only
our claim was cancelled.  At least
10 vehicles are parked here and some vehicles are parked there even before this.
Even after this, some vehicles
which were totally damaged in accidents remained parked.   You have
insurance, right?
Yes, do not take ICICI insurance
ever after today.
Friends, the amount of damage to this car is
too much.  Well, nothing can be known by watching the video on the phone and
talking.   There is a
lot of damage, even here is the roof.  That said,
Hyundai's build
quality is commendable.  Worth watching.  All
six airbags of the car are open.  And there are
three men in it.   There will be and is
Mom, Dad and one special person
who is our friend.  There is some program that day,
he might have taken the car.  So
Hyundai has excellent build quality.
Friends, now let's talk about vehicles.  The Delhi
number car remained with me the whole day.  The remaining
UP number vehicle charged the fare of one Kundli.
And currently it is going for loading.
Where are you going?
I said
Ghaziabad.  Yes, you know everything, are you all-
powerful? That's it.
You know everything. It will go to Ghaziabad.
Yes,
it will be from Perim to
New Zealand. Yes, brother, you will definitely go on the road. It will be
loaded from Perim and after that it will go to
Ghaziabad transport. Currently, my
duty has started on the farm. By the way,
Papa did everything with Sani, he even bathed her, but
I will bathe her again. The car is
asking for all four indicators
and horn. Friends, for now, the fuse of our car has
blown and that will do the job.
Okay Vikas Bhai, look at the video,
your video is uploaded on YouTube, you come, okay,
if I become famous by mistake, it is
fine, I am telling you, I will take money for
advertising your car and your shop,
okay, yes
friends, the indicators of the car have started, there will be a
lot of problem in traffic, by the way, I
took it today as well, I took it yesterday also, you
bastard, don't go,
friends, I am also worried about the mp3 music system, it got
fixed here only.  It was just a matter of fuse.  At
the moment its one thing one thing and
is closed.  Horn and checking.  I think it is
from the steering but it will be checked now and I will know immediately whether it is
from the steering
or from here.  This time also the steering of our car will
come off.
Grace is stuck where it was last
worked on.
She is a thin Nova, not so tall, whose
height and length were increased, Kripa is stuck there
only.  Yes, this is where the
problem lies again.
Last time its length was increased.  It was almost
this much and
this time it became longer.  At present it has been cut and
shortened.   Let's try it and
see if it rings or not.   The problem
in our steering
due to which the horn was not sounding has been
resolved.
But another small problem has arisen in this.   The
gap here in the steering should be
around 1/2 inch.  This gap has reduced.  When it is
hit with a hammer the steering will
rotate downwards.  Meaning he sat down.
So right now the
car is open.  From there he will be
brought up by hitting him.  This is
not a big problem.  The rest
of the work here is done for now.  The other good thing that happened to
me was that I had to get its horn started.  All
four indicators
and one MP3, all these
three tasks were done for me friends.
Everyone in the house is in a bad mood.  At present,
everyone has many memories associated with this car.
Everyone knows that the car has met with an accident.   It's
over.  But this car was not here for three months.
So it was not visible.  So there is no such special
problem.  But right now it
is standing outside the door.
So it is visible to everyone.   What else will happen,
God knows, if it is as per your wish then it is
fine, if not then it is even better,
thank you for staying with us friends, the channel
is yours, do whatever you want, stay happy, stay
busy, stay healthy.